[
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733af5"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "Which side finger print support ?",
        "answer": "In display fingerprint.",
        "likes": 60,
        "dislikes": 15,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733af6"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "Is finger print available ?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "likes": 20,
        "dislikes": 8,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733af7"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "How's the gaming performance ?",
        "answer": "Outstanding Speed Smooth Gaming: 60+ FPS Long Battery Life Highly Recommended for Gamers.",
        "likes": 20,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733af8"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "Is this phone waterproof ir not ?",
        "answer": "It comes with an IP65 rating.",
        "likes": 25,
        "dislikes": 15,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733af9"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "Is 1 sim 1 memory support ?",
        "answer": "No only 2 sim support not memory slot.",
        "likes": 98,
        "dislikes": 8,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733afa"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "Is that Dolby Atmos sound ?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "likes": 22,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733afb"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "Does it have xpandable storage ?",
        "answer": "No",
        "likes": 2,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733afc"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "Is it suitable for wireless charging ?",
        "answer": "No",
        "likes": 12,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733afd"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "How many Os update given in this phone ?",
        "answer": "2 Years of OS update and 3 Years of security update.",
        "likes": 122,
        "dislikes": 24,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733afe"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "Does it support 4k resolution ?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733aff"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "How much zoom of the camera ?",
        "answer": "5x",
        "likes": 6,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b00"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "Is there is NFC ?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 1,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b01"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "Curved display or not ?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "likes": 1,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b02"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "Is tamper glass incuded ?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "likes": 103,
        "dislikes": 13,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b03"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3ce"
        },
        "question": "1 to 100% charging time",
        "answer": "60 min",
        "likes": 45,
        "dislikes": 19,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b04"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3cf"
        },
        "question": "What's size in length x width x height ?",
        "answer": "20cm 14cm 8 cm",
        "likes": 4,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b05"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3cf"
        },
        "question": "How many compartments does this multipurpose toiletry bag have ?",
        "answer": "3",
        "likes": 2,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b06"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3cf"
        },
        "question": "How many Dress can I carry in this bag ?",
        "answer": "10 pairs",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 1,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b07"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d0"
        },
        "question": "What's size in length x width x height ?",
        "answer": "20cm 14cm 8 cm",
        "likes": 4,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b08"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d0"
        },
        "question": "How many compartments does this multipurpose toiletry bag have ?",
        "answer": "3",
        "likes": 2,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b09"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d0"
        },
        "question": "How many Dress can I carry in this bag ?",
        "answer": "10 pairs",
        "likes": 0,
        "dislikes": 1,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b0a"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d1"
        },
        "question": "What is the quantity ?",
        "answer": "1500 ml",
        "likes": 5,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b0b"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d1"
        },
        "question": "Is it better than Santoor handwash ?",
        "answer": "Yeah",
        "likes": 175,
        "dislikes": 74,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b0c"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d1"
        },
        "question": "Does it lather well ?",
        "answer": "Yes it does",
        "likes": 75,
        "dislikes": 14,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b0d"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d1"
        },
        "question": "Does this Dettol handwash refill come with a dispenser bottle ?",
        "answer": "No, this is just a refill pouch, not a dispenser.",
        "likes": 600,
        "dislikes": 34,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b0e"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d1"
        },
        "question": "Is the fragrance of this Dettol handwash mild or strong ?",
        "answer": "The fragrance is mild and pleasant, suitable for daily use.",
        "likes": 12,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b0f"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d1"
        },
        "question": "Can this handwash be used for sensitive skin ?",
        "answer": "Yes, it's designed to be gentle and is suitable for sensitive skin.",
        "likes": 125,
        "dislikes": 19,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b10"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d1"
        },
        "question": "Can this handwash be used for sensitive skin ?",
        "answer": "Yes, it's designed to be gentle and is suitable for sensitive skin.",
        "likes": 125,
        "dislikes": 19,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b11"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d2"
        },
        "question": "Is this shirt made from cotton ?",
        "answer": "Yes, it's 100% cotton.",
        "likes": 125,
        "dislikes": 19,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b12"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d2"
        },
        "question": "Is it a loose-fitting shirt ?",
        "answer": "No, it has a regular fit.",
        "likes": 12,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b13"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d2"
        },
        "question": "Does it have a full sleeve or half sleeve ?",
        "answer": "It's a half-sleeve shirt.",
        "likes": 56,
        "dislikes": 21,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b14"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d2"
        },
        "question": "Is the collar a round neck or a polo collar ?",
        "answer": "It has a polo collar.",
        "likes": 43,
        "dislikes": 9,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b15"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d2"
        },
        "question": "Is this shirt made in India?",
        "answer": "Yes, it's made in India.",
        "likes": 89,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b16"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d3"
        },
        "question": "Does this laptop support VR gaming?",
        "answer": "Yes, the ASUS ROG Strix G16 is VR-ready with its powerful GPU.",
        "likes": 56,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b17"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d3"
        },
        "question": "What is the battery life of this laptop?",
        "answer": "The battery life is approximately 6 hours under normal usage.",
        "likes": 42,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b18"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d3"
        },
        "question": "Can I upgrade the RAM on this laptop?",
        "answer": "Yes, the RAM is upgradeable up to 32GB.",
        "likes": 67,
        "dislikes": 1,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b19"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d3"
        },
        "question": "Does it come with a pre-installed operating system?",
        "answer": "Yes, it comes with Windows 11 pre-installed.",
        "likes": 78,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b1a"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d3"
        },
        "question": "What type of display does this laptop have?",
        "answer": "It has a 16-inch Full HD IPS display with a 144Hz refresh rate.",
        "likes": 89,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b1b"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d3"
        },
        "question": "Is there a fingerprint scanner on this model?",
        "answer": "No, the ASUS ROG Strix G16 does not have a fingerprint scanner.",
        "likes": 33,
        "dislikes": 7,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b1c"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d3"
        },
        "question": "What is the weight of this laptop?",
        "answer": "The laptop weighs approximately 2.3 kg.",
        "likes": 52,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b1d"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d4"
        },
        "question": "Does this refrigerator come with a water dispenser?",
        "answer": "No, this model does not have a water dispenser.",
        "likes": 45,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b1e"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d4"
        },
        "question": "What is the energy rating of this refrigerator?",
        "answer": "This refrigerator has a 3-star energy rating, making it quite energy-efficient.",
        "likes": 58,
        "dislikes": 1,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b1f"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d4"
        },
        "question": "Is the refrigerator suitable for a small family?",
        "answer": "Yes, it's perfect for small families due to its ample storage space.",
        "likes": 67,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b20"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d4"
        },
        "question": "Does it have an inverter compressor?",
        "answer": "Yes, it features a digital inverter compressor for better cooling efficiency.",
        "likes": 50,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b21"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d4"
        },
        "question": "What is the capacity of this refrigerator?",
        "answer": "The refrigerator has a capacity of 252 liters, ideal for moderate usage.",
        "likes": 39,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b22"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d4"
        },
        "question": "Can I adjust the temperature settings?",
        "answer": "Yes, you can easily adjust the temperature settings using the control knob inside.",
        "likes": 42,
        "dislikes": 1,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b23"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d4"
        },
        "question": "Is it noisy during operation?",
        "answer": "No, it's designed to operate quietly, ensuring minimal disturbance.",
        "likes": 35,
        "dislikes": 0,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b24"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d4"
        },
        "question": "Does this model have a built-in stabilizer?",
        "answer": "Yes, it comes with a built-in stabilizer for voltage fluctuations.",
        "likes": 53,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b25"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d4"
        },
        "question": "What warranty does it come with?",
        "answer": "It comes with a 1-year warranty on the product and a 10-year warranty on the compressor.",
        "likes": 40,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b26"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d4"
        },
        "question": "Are the shelves adjustable?",
        "answer": "Yes, the shelves are adjustable to accommodate larger items as needed.",
        "likes": 48,
        "dislikes": 1,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b27"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Does this face wash help with oily skin?",
        "answer": "Yes, it is formulated to control excess oil and reduce shine.",
        "likes": 120,
        "dislikes": 7,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b28"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Is it safe to use daily?",
        "answer": "Yes, this face wash is designed for daily use and is gentle on the skin.",
        "likes": 98,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b29"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Does it contain parabens?",
        "answer": "No, this face wash is free from parabens and other harmful chemicals.",
        "likes": 87,
        "dislikes": 10,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b2a"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Can this face wash be used for sensitive skin?",
        "answer": "Yes, it can be used for sensitive skin, but it's recommended to do a patch test first.",
        "likes": 102,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b2b"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "How long does the brightening effect last?",
        "answer": "The brightening effect is visible for a few hours post-application, but regular use shows longer-lasting results.",
        "likes": 75,
        "dislikes": 12,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b2c"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Is this face wash suitable for teenagers?",
        "answer": "Yes, it can be used by teenagers, but it is primarily targeted for men.",
        "likes": 63,
        "dislikes": 9,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b2d"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Does it help in removing blackheads?",
        "answer": "It helps in deep cleansing and may reduce blackheads with regular use.",
        "likes": 92,
        "dislikes": 6,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b2e"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Is this face wash effective in removing pollution and dirt?",
        "answer": "Yes, it is designed to combat dirt, pollution, and impurities on the skin.",
        "likes": 110,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b2f"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Does this face wash dry out the skin?",
        "answer": "No, it does not excessively dry the skin but leaves it feeling fresh and clean.",
        "likes": 85,
        "dislikes": 11,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b30"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Is it effective for acne-prone skin?",
        "answer": "Yes, it can help reduce acne by controlling oil and deep cleansing the pores.",
        "likes": 117,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b31"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Does it help with skin brightening?",
        "answer": "Yes, the combination of charcoal and vitamin C helps in brightening dull skin.",
        "likes": 130,
        "dislikes": 8,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b32"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Can this be used on a daily basis in winter?",
        "answer": "Yes, but if you have very dry skin, you may need to follow up with a moisturizer.",
        "likes": 81,
        "dislikes": 6,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b33"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Does it contain any harmful chemicals?",
        "answer": "No, this face wash is free from harmful chemicals and uses natural ingredients.",
        "likes": 109,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b34"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Does this face wash have a strong fragrance?",
        "answer": "It has a mild citrus fragrance which is not overpowering.",
        "likes": 77,
        "dislikes": 14,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b35"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "How long does the brightening effect take to show?",
        "answer": "You'll notice a brightening effect immediately after the first use, but long-term benefits come with consistent use.",
        "likes": 118,
        "dislikes": 7,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b36"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d5"
        },
        "question": "Can this be used as a scrub?",
        "answer": "No, this face wash is not a scrub, but it does deep cleanse the skin effectively.",
        "likes": 90,
        "dislikes": 10,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b37"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d6"
        },
        "question": "Does it have active noise cancellation?",
        "answer": "No, it features environmental noise cancellation (ENC) but not active noise cancellation.",
        "likes": 120,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b38"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d6"
        },
        "question": "Can I use these earbuds with an iPhone?",
        "answer": "Yes, these earbuds are compatible with any device that supports Bluetooth, including iPhones.",
        "likes": 98,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b39"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d6"
        },
        "question": "How long does the battery last on a single charge?",
        "answer": "The earbuds can last up to 50 hours of playtime with the charging case.",
        "likes": 86,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b3a"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d6"
        },
        "question": "Is this product water-resistant?",
        "answer": "Yes, it has an IPX5 rating, making it resistant to sweat and light splashes.",
        "likes": 105,
        "dislikes": 8,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b3b"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d6"
        },
        "question": "Can I use only one earbud at a time?",
        "answer": "Yes, you can use either of the earbuds independently.",
        "likes": 78,
        "dislikes": 6,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b3c"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d6"
        },
        "question": "Does it come with a charging cable?",
        "answer": "Yes, the earbuds come with a USB Type-C charging cable.",
        "likes": 91,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b3d"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d6"
        },
        "question": "How is the sound quality of these earbuds?",
        "answer": "The earbuds deliver clear sound with deep bass, thanks to the 13mm drivers.",
        "likes": 130,
        "dislikes": 7,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b3e"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d6"
        },
        "question": "Do these earbuds support fast charging?",
        "answer": "Yes, they support Instacharge, giving 120 minutes of playtime with just 10 minutes of charging.",
        "likes": 102,
        "dislikes": 9,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b3f"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d6"
        },
        "question": "Is there a low-latency mode for gaming?",
        "answer": "Yes, the earbuds feature Hyper Sync technology for low-latency audio.",
        "likes": 87,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b40"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d6"
        },
        "question": "What is the Bluetooth version on these earbuds?",
        "answer": "These earbuds use Bluetooth version 5.2 for seamless connectivity.",
        "likes": 93,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b41"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d7"
        },
        "question": "Is this bottle microwave-safe?",
        "answer": "Yes, since it's made of borosilicate glass, it is microwave-safe.",
        "likes": 56,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b42"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d7"
        },
        "question": "Can I store hot liquids in this bottle?",
        "answer": "Yes, the borosilicate glass can withstand high temperatures, making it suitable for hot liquids.",
        "likes": 72,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b43"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d7"
        },
        "question": "Does this bottle come with a carrying sleeve?",
        "answer": "No, the bottle does not come with a carrying sleeve.",
        "likes": 43,
        "dislikes": 7,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b44"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d7"
        },
        "question": "Is the bottle dishwasher-safe?",
        "answer": "Yes, this bottle is dishwasher-safe for easy cleaning.",
        "likes": 89,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b45"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d7"
        },
        "question": "What is the weight of the bottle when empty?",
        "answer": "The bottle weighs approximately 350 grams when empty.",
        "likes": 65,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b46"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d7"
        },
        "question": "Does the bottle retain any odor after washing?",
        "answer": "No, borosilicate glass is odor-resistant and does not retain smells.",
        "likes": 80,
        "dislikes": 6,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b47"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d7"
        },
        "question": "Can this bottle fit in a standard car cup holder?",
        "answer": "No, due to its 1-liter capacity, it might be too large for most car cup holders.",
        "likes": 50,
        "dislikes": 10,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b48"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d7"
        },
        "question": "Is the bottle suitable for travel?",
        "answer": "Yes, the bottle is durable and suitable for travel.",
        "likes": 77,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b49"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d7"
        },
        "question": "What is the diameter of the bottle's mouth?",
        "answer": "The bottle has a wide mouth of approximately 5 cm, making it easy to clean.",
        "likes": 92,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b4a"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d7"
        },
        "question": "Can I store carbonated drinks in this bottle?",
        "answer": "It’s not recommended to store carbonated drinks in this bottle as it is not designed for pressure.",
        "likes": 60,
        "dislikes": 8,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b4b"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d8"
        },
        "question": "Are these flip flops suitable for outdoor use?",
        "answer": "Yes, they are designed for both indoor and outdoor use.",
        "likes": 75,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b4c"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d8"
        },
        "question": "What material are these flip flops made of?",
        "answer": "They are made of lightweight, durable rubber material.",
        "likes": 82,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b4d"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d8"
        },
        "question": "Do these flip flops have arch support?",
        "answer": "Yes, they provide moderate arch support for comfort.",
        "likes": 90,
        "dislikes": 1,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b4e"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d8"
        },
        "question": "Are these flip flops available in different colors?",
        "answer": "Yes, they come in a variety of colors to choose from.",
        "likes": 70,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b4f"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d8"
        },
        "question": "Can I wear these flip flops at the beach?",
        "answer": "Absolutely! They are perfect for the beach and water activities.",
        "likes": 88,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b50"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d8"
        },
        "question": "Are these flip flops easy to clean?",
        "answer": "Yes, you can easily clean them with soap and water.",
        "likes": 79,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b51"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d8"
        },
        "question": "What sizes are available for these flip flops?",
        "answer": "They are available in various sizes from S to XL.",
        "likes": 65,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b52"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d8"
        },
        "question": "Do these flip flops have a non-slip sole?",
        "answer": "Yes, they feature a non-slip sole for better grip.",
        "likes": 85,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b53"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d8"
        },
        "question": "How do I determine the right size for these flip flops?",
        "answer": "Refer to the size chart provided in the product details for accurate sizing.",
        "likes": 72,
        "dislikes": 6,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b54"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d8"
        },
        "question": "Are these flip flops comfortable for all-day wear?",
        "answer": "Yes, they are designed for comfort, making them suitable for all-day wear.",
        "likes": 94,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b55"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d9"
        },
        "question": "Is this dishwash gel safe for washing vegetables?",
        "answer": "Yes, it is safe and effective for cleaning vegetables and fruits.",
        "likes": 120,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b56"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d9"
        },
        "question": "Does this gel leave a residue on dishes?",
        "answer": "No, it rinses off completely, leaving no residue behind.",
        "likes": 98,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b57"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d9"
        },
        "question": "How many washes can I get from a 2 Ltr pouch?",
        "answer": "You can get approximately 100 washes, depending on usage.",
        "likes": 85,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b58"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d9"
        },
        "question": "Is the lemon scent strong?",
        "answer": "Yes, it has a refreshing lemon scent that helps eliminate odors.",
        "likes": 110,
        "dislikes": 1,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b59"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d9"
        },
        "question": "Can I use this gel with a dishwashing machine?",
        "answer": "No, this gel is designed for handwashing dishes only.",
        "likes": 67,
        "dislikes": 6,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b5a"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d9"
        },
        "question": "Is this product biodegradable?",
        "answer": "Yes, it is formulated to be biodegradable and environmentally friendly.",
        "likes": 95,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b5b"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d9"
        },
        "question": "Does this gel effectively remove grease?",
        "answer": "Yes, it cuts through tough grease and food residue effortlessly.",
        "likes": 123,
        "dislikes": 1,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b5c"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d9"
        },
        "question": "Is this dishwash gel suitable for sensitive skin?",
        "answer": "It is mild, but it's best to wear gloves if you have very sensitive skin.",
        "likes": 80,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b5d"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d9"
        },
        "question": "How does this product compare to regular dish soap?",
        "answer": "Vim Dishwash Gel offers superior grease-cutting power compared to regular dish soaps.",
        "likes": 90,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b5e"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3d9"
        },
        "question": "Where can I store the refill pouch?",
        "answer": "Store the refill pouch in a cool, dry place away from direct sunlight.",
        "likes": 75,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b5f"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3da"
        },
        "question": "Does this scooter require RTO registration?",
        "answer": "No, it does not require RTO registration or a driving license.",
        "likes": 95,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b60"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3da"
        },
        "question": "What is the maximum speed of this electric scooter?",
        "answer": "The scooter can reach a maximum speed of 25 km/h.",
        "likes": 88,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b61"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3da"
        },
        "question": "How far can I travel on a full charge?",
        "answer": "You can travel up to 30 kilometers on a full charge.",
        "likes": 102,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b62"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3da"
        },
        "question": "What type of battery does it use?",
        "answer": "It comes with a portable rechargeable battery that is easy to remove.",
        "likes": 76,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b63"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3da"
        },
        "question": "Is the scooter suitable for taller individuals?",
        "answer": "Yes, it features a comfortable wider deck to accommodate various heights.",
        "likes": 90,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b64"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3da"
        },
        "question": "How long does it take to fully charge the battery?",
        "answer": "It takes approximately 4-6 hours to fully charge the battery.",
        "likes": 84,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b65"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3da"
        },
        "question": "Is there any assembly required when I receive the scooter?",
        "answer": "Minimal assembly is required; basic tools are included in the package.",
        "likes": 78,
        "dislikes": 6,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b66"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3da"
        },
        "question": "Can I ride this scooter in the rain?",
        "answer": "It's best to avoid riding in heavy rain, but light splashes shouldn't damage it.",
        "likes": 66,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b67"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3da"
        },
        "question": "What kind of terrain is this scooter suitable for?",
        "answer": "It's designed for smooth roads and pavements; not recommended for rough terrain.",
        "likes": 71,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b68"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3da"
        },
        "question": "Does it come with any warranty?",
        "answer": "Yes, it typically comes with a 1-year warranty on the motor and battery.",
        "likes": 82,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b69"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3db"
        },
        "question": "Does this phone support 5G?",
        "answer": "No, the POCO C65 supports 4G LTE but does not have 5G capability.",
        "likes": 95,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b6a"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3db"
        },
        "question": "Is the storage expandable?",
        "answer": "Yes, you can expand the storage up to 1TB with a microSD card.",
        "likes": 104,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b6b"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3db"
        },
        "question": "Does the phone come with a screen protector?",
        "answer": "No, it doesn't come with a screen protector, but you can purchase one separately.",
        "likes": 72,
        "dislikes": 6,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b6c"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3db"
        },
        "question": "What is the battery capacity?",
        "answer": "The phone has a large 5000mAh battery, providing extended usage time.",
        "likes": 110,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b6d"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3db"
        },
        "question": "Does it have a fingerprint sensor?",
        "answer": "Yes, the POCO C65 has a side-mounted fingerprint sensor.",
        "likes": 88,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b6e"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3db"
        },
        "question": "Can I use dual SIM cards with this phone?",
        "answer": "Yes, it supports dual SIM cards and a microSD card simultaneously.",
        "likes": 90,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b6f"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3db"
        },
        "question": "What version of Android does it run?",
        "answer": "The phone runs on Android 12 with MIUI for POCO.",
        "likes": 76,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b70"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3db"
        },
        "question": "Is the back panel made of glass or plastic?",
        "answer": "The back panel is made of durable plastic with a matte finish.",
        "likes": 83,
        "dislikes": 7,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b71"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3db"
        },
        "question": "Does it support fast charging?",
        "answer": "Yes, the POCO C65 supports 18W fast charging.",
        "likes": 101,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b72"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3db"
        },
        "question": "What type of display does the phone have?",
        "answer": "It features a 6.5-inch HD+ IPS LCD display with a resolution of 1600x720 pixels.",
        "likes": 92,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b73"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3dc"
        },
        "question": "Does this smartwatch support Bluetooth calling?",
        "answer": "Yes, it has Bluetooth calling capability, allowing you to make and receive calls directly from the watch.",
        "likes": 102,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b74"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3dc"
        },
        "question": "How many sports modes are available?",
        "answer": "The Fire-Boltt Apollo 2 offers over 100 sports modes for various activities.",
        "likes": 85,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b75"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3dc"
        },
        "question": "Is this watch compatible with iOS?",
        "answer": "Yes, it is compatible with both iOS and Android devices.",
        "likes": 77,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b76"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3dc"
        },
        "question": "Does it have an always-on display feature?",
        "answer": "Yes, the AMOLED display supports an always-on display mode.",
        "likes": 90,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b77"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3dc"
        },
        "question": "Is the watch waterproof?",
        "answer": "The watch is IP67 water-resistant, which makes it splash and sweat-resistant.",
        "likes": 110,
        "dislikes": 6,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b78"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3dc"
        },
        "question": "How long does the battery last on a full charge?",
        "answer": "It typically lasts up to 5 days on a single charge, depending on usage.",
        "likes": 92,
        "dislikes": 3,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b79"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3dc"
        },
        "question": "Does this watch have a heart rate monitor?",
        "answer": "Yes, it includes a heart rate monitor as part of its health suite.",
        "likes": 88,
        "dislikes": 4,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b7a"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3dc"
        },
        "question": "Can I control music on my phone with this watch?",
        "answer": "Yes, you can control music playback on your phone via the smartwatch.",
        "likes": 74,
        "dislikes": 6,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b7b"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3dc"
        },
        "question": "Does the smartwatch support voice assistants?",
        "answer": "Yes, it has a built-in voice assistant for easy hands-free operation.",
        "likes": 99,
        "dislikes": 2,
        "__v": 0
    },
    {
        "_id": {
            "$oid": "670babb0d14d5d29c0733b7c"
        },
        "product_id": {
            "$oid": "670b90f849af9bf770efd3dc"
        },
        "question": "What is the size of the display?",
        "answer": "The watch features a 36.3mm (1.43 inch) AMOLED display.",
        "likes": 84,
        "dislikes": 5,
        "__v": 0
    }
]